Stu Brewster here,
and I'd like you all
스투 브루스터입니다
미사일 커맨드의 새로운 세계 챔피언인
to meet Jeffery Barnes, the new
Missile Command world champ.
SAN FERNANO VALLEY, 1983
제프리 반즈씨께서 나와계십니다
1983년 샌 퍼나노 밸리
VALLEY VIDEO GAME
CHAMPIONSHIPS
Thanks for
joining us, Jeff.
제프 이렇게 나와주셔서 감사합니다
My pleasure, Stu.
천만에요 스투
Now, Jeff,
you've dedicated the last
제프, 지난 3년 내내
미사일 커맨드를 하시면서
three years of your life
to playing Missile Command.
You've managed
to take a video game
이 게임을 정복하고
예술의 경지에까지 이르셨다고 들었습니다
and raise it to a level
that can only be
described as an art form.
So let me ask
자 제가 모든 분들이
알고 싶어하시는걸 여쭤볼게요
the question on
everybody's mind:
What's next
for Jeff Barnes?
다음 목표는 뭐죠?
What's next? Uh...
다음이요? 음..
I hadn't really, uh...
아직 생각을..
How can I make up my mind
이렇게나 멋진 선택권들이 잔뜩 있는데
when I've got
so many tasty options?
어떻게 결정하겠어요?
I've got so many tasty options.
맛있는 선택권이 잔뜩 있어
(tasty : 맛있는, 멋진)
SAN FERNANDO VALLEY
25 YEARS LATER
25년 후. 샌 퍼나도 밸리
Jeff, please.
제프 제발
There we go, buddy.
자 이거 먹어
Score.
아싸
Powwow on the
sales floor.
매장에서 회의 있다
And one of you two idiots better
light a fire under Bartowski.
너희 멍청이들
바토스키한테 일 똑바로 하라 그래
He's late.
지각이잖아
Aren't you
forgetting something?
뭐 잊은 것 없어?
It's only the most important
meal of the day, bud.
이게 세 끼중 가장 중요한거야
Of course!
물론이지
Breakfast.
아침 먹어야지
Thanks.
고마워요
What did I... What is that?
이거, 이거 뭐야?
나 방금 뭐 마신거야
What did I just drink?
It's a ginseng
protein shake.
인삼 단백질 쉐이크야
Been used
thousands of years
이걸 동방에선 수 천년간
양기 보충하는데 마셨대
in the East
to promote Yang energy.
And let me tell you, brother,
내가 뭐 하나 알려줄까
it does wonders
for your wang energy.
이게 거기에 그렇게 좋대
Great, thanks.
잘 됐네 고마워
Hey, where were you last night?
척, 어제 어디 있었어?
We heard you come
stomping in at, like,
새벽 4시였나
너 들어오는 소리 들었어
4:00 in the morning.
Yeah, oh, yeah, it was a...
it was a crazy night.
응, 응
어젯밤에 정신 없었거든
Morgan and I stole a car,
and then we drove around
모건이랑 차 훔쳐서 돌아다니고
술집도 가고 창녀들이랑 놀았거든
shaking down liquor stores
and smacking around hookers.
Relax, it's a video game.
진정해
그냥 비디오 게임이니까
Oh, good... video games.
그래. 비디오 게임이라니
Come on, El.
I mean, what's one night
엘리 그만해
하루 쯤은 놀아도 되잖아
- of blowing off a little steam?
- One nights have
오늘만 오늘만 하다가
계속 하는거야
a funny way of adding up.
I mean, what's cool
when you're in college...
물론 네가 대학생이면
상관없지만..
We were just wondering...
우리가 하고 싶은말은..
what happened
to all your big plans, bro?
그 큰 계획들은 어떻게 된거야?
All that talk about
backpacking across Europe,
유럽으로 여행가는거나
대학으로 다시 돌아가는건?
or finishing
your college classes?
You know, I just have a lot on
my plate at this precise moment.
지금 당장은 해야 할 일이 많아서 그래
Well, like what, precisely?
정확하게 그게 뭔데?
Chuck, we were happy when you
decided not to move out,
척. 네가 여기 머물기로
결정한 건 정말 기쁘지만
but shouldn't your life
be moving somewhere?
네 인생은 앞으로
나아가야 하지 않을까?
It's time for you people
이제 자네들이 열심히 일 해야 할때야
to get moving around here.
Show some initiative!
솔선수범해서!
Well, I've got
just the guy to help.
그래서 자네들을
도우실 분을 모셨네
I'd like you to meet
Emmett Milbarge.
여긴 에밋 밀바지씨다
Emmett here's an efficiency
expert, and he's been sent
에밋씨는 능률 전문가로
게을러빠진 너네들을 정신 차리게 하려고
by Buy More corporate
to tighten your slack-asses up.
바이모어 본사에서 초대하신 분이다
Thank you for your very kind
words of introduction, Michael.
소개 감사합니다. 마이클씨
I'll be in my office.
전 사무실에 가 있죠
Well, it is just
so nice to be here in...
음 일단 이렇게 여기..
Burbank.
버뱅크요
Burbank, California.
캘리포니아 버뱅크에 와서 기쁩니다
Just a real pleasure
이렇게 직접 만나게 되어서
정말 반갑고요
to meet all of you
in the flesh.
I personally am
개인적으로는 여기 바이모어에서
looking forward
to spending more time here
in the Buy More trenches,
더 많은 시간을 보내고 싶어요
getting to know
the rank and the file.
여러분들과 친해지면서 말이죠
Unfortunately,
my visit here
하지만 안타깝게도 제가 여기
머무는게 즐겁지만은 않으실겁니다
isn't going to be all fun.
I'm going to be
interviewing you,
전 여러분들을 인터뷰하고
and I'm going to be evaluating
you on your performance,
성과를 바탕으로
여러분들을 평가할 예정입니다
And, perhaps, even...
그리고 심지어..
trimming the fat.
지방까지도 말입니다
So... who would like
to go first?
자 그럼
누가 먼저 하시겠습니까?
We'll just start out simple.
간단하게 시작하죠
Why do you
belong at the Buy More?
왜 바이모어에서 일하시죠?
I satisfy a quota.
쿼터제가 마음에 들어서요
(일정비율 외국인을 고용해야하는 제도)
My dad's part Indian.
아버지가 인도 혈통이시거든요
The cool kind of Indian,
though, not like Lester.
멋진 인도 쪽이요
레스터 같은 쪽 말고요
I used to be
in management, myself,
저도 경영 분야에
몸을 담은 적이 있죠
so I know how
그래서 매장을 운영하는
법에 대해선 압니다...
to grease the store's... cogs.
속임수죠
- "Cogs"?
- Make sure they don't...
속임수요?
사람들이..
squeak.
고자질 못하게 막는거죠
If you know what I'm saying.
무슨 말인지 아시죠
ASS-KISSER
아부쟁이
Why do I belong at the Buy More?
왜 바이모어에서 일하냐고요?
You know, I'm going to have
to think about that.
저기 생각을 해봐야겠어요
I'm going to go
grab a soda.
가서 사이다 좀 마셔야겠어요
And... You want one?
아 한 잔 드릴까요?
제가 살게요
'Cause it's my treat.
I'll gr- I'll grab you one.
제가, 제가 한 잔 가져다 드릴게요
And I'll be back in a jiff.
금방 다시 올게요
UNTRAINABLE
훈련 불가능
I speak more than one language,
binary code.
영어 말고 다른 말도 할 줄 알아요
2진 코드요
Zero, zero, zero, one,
0, 0, 0, 1
one, zero,
1, 0
one... zero.
1... 0
PROSTITUTE?
창녀?
What would I do?
제가 어떻게 하겠냐고요?
I'd just ask W-W-C-D?
척.어.하라고 묻겠어요
- "What would Chuck do?"
- Chuck?
- "척은 어떻게 할까?"
- 척이요?
The chain of command?
지휘 계통이요?
Well, there's, like, Chuck,
그건 척하고.. 나머지 모두죠
and then there's, like,
the rest of us.
Oh, and then there's Jeff.
아 또 제프도요
Sometimes I... W-W-C-D-N?
전 가끔은 지.척.뭐 라고 묻기도 하죠
"Wonder what Chuck's doing now?"
"지금 척은 뭐할까?"
Who represents
the Buy More ideal?
누가 바이모어의 이상을 대표하죠?
Who makes the trains
run on time?
매장을 제대로 돌아가게 하는 사람은 누구죠?
Who provides your moral compass?
도덕적 문제에 있어서
누가 도움을 주나요?
Who holds
the team together?
누가 직원들을 단결시키죠?
- Chuck.
- 척이요
Lester... no, Chuck.
레스터..
아니 척이요
- Chuck.
- Well...
- 척이요
- 그렇군요
I'm looking forward
to meeting this Chuck fella.
척이란 친구를 만나보고 싶네요
If he ever decides to show up.
출근을 하긴 한다면 말이죠
Chuck, you picked one hell
of a morning to be late.
척. 늦어도 꼭 이런 날 늦냐
- Yeah, crazy night, Morgan.
- Lover's tryst?
- 그러게. 어젯밤에 정신이 없었어
- 새라랑 만났어?
Say no more.
말 안 해줘도 돼
Unless you care to infuse
your story with a more
야한 얘기까지
아주 자세하게 해줄 것 아니면
tawdry level of detail?
You don't. Okay, listen,
there's this efficiency guy
안 해줄거지. 알았어
능률 전문가란 사람이 왔는데
who's been looking all over
for you, all right.
계속 널 찾고 있어
So if he asks, you have
gallstone issues.
혹시라도 만나면
담석때문에 아팠다고 그래
- That's a thing, right?
- Morgan?
- 그렇게 해. 알겠지?
- 모건?
Well, I had to think
on my feet here, Chuck.
급하게 생각해내느라 그랬어
This Emmett guy's
been busting my...
그 사람이 완전 내..
preconceptions.
편견을 깨주셨어
And helping me see the Buy More
또 바이모어를 새로운 시각으로 보게..
오 안녕하세요!
in a whole new...
Hey, hello!
This is him... Chuck.
바로 이 분이셔. 척
We finally meet, Chuck.
드디어 만났군요 척
Hi.
안녕하세요
SOMALIA TRAINING CAMPS
DIRTY BOMB TRADE
소말리아 훈련소
방사능 폭탄 거래
NUCLEAR WEAPONS TRAINING
핵 무기 훈련
Are you feeling all right?
괜찮아요?
No- yes!
아니요. 네
Yes, I'm fine.
네 괜찮아요
Actually on second thought,
사실 다시 생각해보니까
I think my gallstones
are acting up, so...
담석때문에 좀 아픈 것 같네요
Hi.
안녕하세요
Do you know this man?
이 사람 아십니까?
No. No, never
아니요 몰라요
단 한 번도 본 적 없어요
seen him before
in my life.
Wait a minute.
Is that one of the sweat hogs
잠시만요
이 사람 웰컴 백, 카터에 나왔던
from Welcome Back, Kotter?
스윗 혹스 멤버 중 하나 아니예요?
(1970년대 미국 시트콤)
He is a Buy More employee.
바이모어 직원입니다
You know, he doesn't work
at this store.
여기서 일하는 사람은 아닌 것 같네요
But you should check out
one of our other
하지만 동부 캘리포니아에는 다른
13개 매장도 있으니까 그 쪽도 확인해 보세요
13 convenient
Southern California locations.
Hmm...
굶俚캥쏭묩欺構슥직，拮쐐痰黨庚둡촐
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://www.nate.com/24)
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
CHUCK 205
영어자막 : www.shooter.cn
싱크수정 / 한글자막
김호정 (hojeong_@nate.com)
수정 금지 / 배포 자유
배포시 출처를 밝혀주세요
-=팎읔襟俚캥莉=-
珂쇌菉:乖갖哥懃鬼s
Chuck 2x05
Chuck Versus Tom Sawyer
Farrokh Bulsara,
파로크 불사라
CLASSIFIED
born in the Asir Province, 1974.
1974년 사우디 아라비아
아시르에서 출생
The past ten years,
he's been hopping
지난 10년간 시리아와 소말리아에
있는 훈련소들을 담당했어
between training camps
from Syria to Somalia.
What does a global terrorist
want with a nerd like Jeff?
국제 테러리스트가
제프 같은 애를 왜 찾는거예요?
Insightful question,
Bartowski.
통찰력 있는 질문이야. 바토스키
It's why we have
an Intersect.
그래서 인터섹트가 있는거지
We want you to approach
Jeff socially.
제프하고 친해져서
Get to know him
better and see
좀 더 가까워지고
과거에 대해서 알아내 보세요
if you can get
him to open up
about his past.
You want me to hang out
with Jeff?
제프랑 같이 어울리라는거예요?
It's either that, or we throw
him in the back of a van
싫으면 밴에 처박아놓고
and have an agency interrogation
team go to work on him.
기관에서 심문 팀 파견할게
Great, so it comes down
to either torturing him
잘됐네요. 제프를 괴롭히거나
날 괴롭히겠다는거에요?
or torturing me?
Looks like we got a bogey.
누가 왔어요
Sarah?
새라?
Is that my sister?
우리 누나예요?
Ellie, what a surprise.
엘리. 여긴 어쩐 일이예요
Yeah, I was just driving around
네 그냥 지나가다가
우리 둘이..
I thought it'd
be nice, uh...
I thought it would be nice
if you and I could talk
척 없이 우리 둘이 얘기하고 싶어서요
without Chuck, actually.
Oh, okay.
오 그래요
Not polite
to spy, Chuck.
엿들으면 안 돼지, 척
I would hate it if he found out
that I was going
내가 척 모르게 여기 온 거
척한테는 말하지 마세요
behind his back
like this.
Oh, well, your secret
is safe with me.
그럼요. 비밀 지킬게요
Do you know if he has any plans?
척이 계획하는 일
뭐 아는거 있어요?
Tonight?
오늘 밤이요?
Uh, actually, I think he is
hanging out with Jeff.
음 오늘 제프하고 논다고 하던데요
Nerd Herd, creepy, serial-killer
Jeff?
같이 일한다는 그 소름끼치는
연쇄 살인범 제프요?
Yeah.
- 네
- 우리 얘기 좀 해요
I think it's time
that you and I had a talk.
I hope you enjoyed
your fro-yo?
요구르트 아이스크림 잘 먹었어요?
Ha. Yeah, I was,
uh, just seeing my girlfriend.
네. 그냥 여자친구 만나러 간 거예요
Girlfriend? Oh...
여자 친구요?
I, too, have
a special lady friend.
저도 특별한 여자 친구가 있어요
Henrietta.
헨리에타라고
She works in our Ontario branch,
accounts payable.
바이모어 온타리오 지점
지급 관리팀에서 일해요
She's a real tigress.
정말 사나운 여자죠
Well, now that
we've gotten the topic
얘기가 이상한 쪽으로 흘렀네요
of our love life out of the way,
perhaps you'd like to sit
down for our interview.
그럼 이제 인터뷰를 시작해 볼까요
How is tomorrow?
내일은 어떠세요?
'Cause I'm really more
of a morning person.
제가 아침형 인간이라서요
I'll be the judge of that.
그건 내가 판단하죠
Hey, buddy.
Where are you going?
안녕 제프. 어디 가?
What'd I do?
내가 뭘?
Nothing! No.
아니야 아무것도 아니야
You know... nothing.
아무것도 아니야
Just... you know, we never
really get the chance to talk.
우리끼리 말할 기회가 별로 없었잖아
How about we grab a beer?
맥주 한 잔 마시러 갈까?
No, thanks.
아니 됐어
I could be enticed
to grab a dozen beers, however.
하지만 맥주 여러 잔이라면 마실 수 있어
It's a date.
오늘 가자
We can kick it at my place.
우리 집에서 마셔도 돼
You're going
to love Roscoe.
너도 로스코보면 좋아할거야
He's my ferret.
내가 키우는 족제비 이름이야
Ooh... you know what?
아.. 있잖아
그게 사실 내가
I'm actually allergic
족제비과 동물들에
알레르기가 있거든
to any and every member
of the polecat family.
So maybe we can kick it here?
그니까 그냥 여기서 마시는 건 어때?
Sure.
그러지 뭐
- Hmm.
- Hmm...
Following a thorough inspection
of the branch,
이 지점에 대한 철저한 검사를 한 결과
there seems to be no sign
이 곳엔 이성적인 사람이
단 한 사람도 없음
of intelligent life.
May I present
자 오늘의 특별한 순서야
tonight's feature entertainment.
You made an Anna music video?
애나로 뮤직비디오를 만든거야?
You like?
맘에 들어?
Wow.
우와
It's really-
이거 정말..
Wow.
우와
I know, man.
나도 알아
She's my muse.
애나가 내 뮤즈야
Now, if you'll excuse me.
그럼 난 음주용 바지 입으러
잠시 실례할게
I'm going to slip
into my drinking pants.
Look at that!
이런!
Abort mission.
Extraction required.
미션 실패
탈출 해야함
The Intersect
has been compromised.
인터섹트가 위험하다
Negative.
Perimeter is secure.
아니야
주변은 이상 없어
I'm talking about the weirdo
inside the Buy More!
바이모어 안에 있는
정신병자 얘길 하는거예요!
I'm starting to think
척한테 무슨 일이 있는 것 같아요
that there's something
going on with my brother.
Oh.
오
Why?
왜요? 무슨 말씀이세요?
What do you mean?
It's just
everything seemed
모든 일이 척한테 좋게
흘러간다고 생각했어요
to be moving along
just fine for Chuck.
And you had everything
to do with that.
그 모든게 새라 덕분이겠죠
Oh, thanks,
오 고마워요
but, uh, I-I can't
take the credit.
그치만 저 때문은 아니예요
Then, I don't know,
it's like...
근데 모르겠어요
갑자기..
it's like he's slipping
back into old Chuck mode.
예전의 척으로 돌아간 것 같아요
You know, no
confidence.
알죠, 자신감도 없고
목표도 없는거요
No direction.
It's-
it's the Morgan
Years revisited.
예전에 모건이랑 놀 때처럼요
I mean he went to
Stanford, for God's sakes.
세상에 스탠포드에 다니던 애라고요
Did you know that he's 12
credits short of graduating?
졸업학점에서 12학점 부족했던거 알아요?
12 credits short of a real life.
현실에서 12학점 부족하다고요
I know that I sound
like his mother.
내가 꼭 엄마처럼 군다는거 알아요
Just tell me that I don't have
걱정할 것 없다고 해주면
이제 그만 괴롭힐게요
anything to worry about
and I will lay off.
Pound! Pound! Pound!
마셔 마셔 마셔!
Go! Yes!
그래! 그렇지!
Pound! Pound!
마셔 마셔!
Quit being such
a lightweight!
이제 살 좀 쪄!
Resuming dictation.
구술을 추가한다
Yes! Yes!
그래! 그렇지!
I'd like to report the following
violation of Buy More policy:
바이모어 방침에 어긋나는
다음의 상황을 보고할 것
misappropriation
홈 시어터 방의 남용
of the home theater room,
after hours
근무 시간후 알콜 소비
consumption of alcohol.
And lewd use
of a musical montage.
혼성 음악 효과의 외설적 사용
I'm going hohome at once
to file this report.
Crazy thing happened today.
오늘 이상한 일이 있었어
Uh, some dude came into the
store looking for you.
어떤 남자가 매장에 찾아와서
널 찾더라
He had this goofy,
바보 같이 나온 예전 사진을 들고 있었어
old picture and
everything.
Only a matter of time, I guess.
이젠 시간 문제겠지
What?
뭐?
You mean you
know the guy?
그 남자, 아는 사람이라는거야?
I'd imagine...
아마도..
he's one of my fans.
내 팬들 중 하나일거야
You want to see something
I've never shared with anyone?
아무한테도 안 보여준건데
볼래?
Please don't be a porno.
제발 포르노가 아니길
- Please, please don't be a porno.
- And I'd like you all
제발. 제발 포르노가 아니길
미사일 커맨드의 새로운 세계 챔피언인
제프리 반즈씨께서 나와계십니다
to meet Jeffery Barnes.
The new Missile Command
world champ.
Missile Command?
미사일 커맨드라고?
I used to kick ass at that game.
나 그 게임 진짜 잘했는데
Well, I was the best.
그래도 내가 최고였지
By breaking the all-time record,
모든 기록을 깸으로써
you've won $100 in quarters
상금 100달러와
and a year's supply
of Slim Jim's.
1년간 슬림 짐을 무상 제공 받게되셨습니다
(스낵 이름)
This prize will be presented
이 상은 아타리 게임회사의 CEO이자
by none other
than Mr. Morimoto, CEO
기술책임장인 모리모토씨가
직접 수여하시겠습니다
and chief engineer
at Atari games.
Dude, you are
so wasted.
야 너 너무 취했다
FACIAL SCANNING
안면 인식 중
COMPLETE
FARROKH BULSARA
검색 완료
파로크 불사라
What is it
나쁜 놈들과 밴이라니
이게 무슨 일이야
about bad guys and vans?
Okay.
Okay, Chuck,
party's over.
자 척. 파티는 끝났어
Hey, hey,
케이시 떠올랐어요
티비에서 봤는데 비디오..
I- I flashed! Some guy
on the TV. He's a video...
Later, Chuck. We have guests.
Out the back door. Now!
나중에 해. 누가 나타났어
뒷문으로 나가 빨리!
- Wait, wait, wait, wait, what about Jeff?
- What about him?
- 잠깐 잠깐. 제프는 어쩌고요?
- 얘가 뭐?
- We can't just leave him here.
- He's deadweight.
- 여기 두고 가면 안 돼죠
- 데려가봤자 짐만 돼
You weren't kidding.
당신 말이 맞았어요
Go! Go!
빨리 와!
He pukes on my
upholstery,
쟤가 내 차에 토하면
he's gonna wish we left him
with the terrorists.
테러리스트한테 버려졌길
바라게 만들어줄거야
Search the place.
뒤져 봐
Should I be worried about him?
걱정을 해야 할까요?
You know, um, Chuck is, uh...
알다시피 척은..
Chuck is like a duck.
오리 같잖아요
Sometimes
때때로는 조용히 지나다니는 것 같지만
it seems like
he is just gliding along,
but beneath the surface,
물 아래로는 작은 발로
엄청나게 헤엄치고 있는거예요
his, uh... his little feet
are-are just
paddling away like crazy.
Deep down,
마음 속으로는 정말 성숙하고
I really think
Chuck is an incredibly mature
책임감 있는 사람이라고 생각해요
and responsible guy.
Chuck?
척?
Oh!
- Oh,
- is he okay?
걔 괜찮아?
Yeah. Don't worry.
This guy's feeling no pain.
응 걱정마
아무것도 못 느낄거야
Ouch.
Here we go. Here we go.
자 다 왔어
Big boy. Big boy.
정말 무겁다
What's up, ladies?
안녕하세요 숙녀분들
You take the brunette.
갈색 머리는 너 가져
I'm gonna take a crack
at the blonde.
난 금발머리 가질게
???
이 자식
Oh...! Jeff!
제프!
I'm, uh, supposed
to give this to you.
이거 좀 보세요
MY NAME IS JEFF AND I'M LOST
제 이름은 제프입니다
길을 잃었어요
Okay.
그래요
이게 집 주소예요?
Is that your address?
- Yeah.
- All right, we're gonna get you a cab.
- 네
- 알았어요 택시 불러줄게요
Already have.
Already here. Thank you.
이미 불렀어
도착했어 고마워
Great. Awesome.
Come on, Jeff.
좋았어 짱이다
이리 와 제프
That was a great
time last night, huh?
어젯 밤에 재밌었지?
You got smashed
and passed out,
너 술 취해서 쓰러지는걸
and we just watched, and
it was really awkward.
우리가 보고있는데
정말 곤란하더라
Okay, here
you go, buddy.
자 이제 가
Get home safe.
조심히 들어가
Chuck.
척
We're about to have one of
those conversations, aren't we?
우리 또 그 얘기 할꺼지?
Well, if I wasn't
worried enough,
내가 충분히 걱정한게 아니었다면
last night's
performance was...
어젯 밤 일들은..
Not... Not one of
my proudest moments.
나한테도 자랑스러운 순간은 아니었어
Uh-uh.
그래
I feel like you left
all those back at Stanford.
난 네가 스탠포드에
모든 걸 두고 온 것 같아
I'm sorry. I just...
미안해 내 말은..
You were so close to graduating.
금방이면 졸업할 수 있었잖아
You know, maybe if you just
went back and finished,
네가 다시 돌아가서
학교를 끝마쳤으면
you could move on
to the next phase.
지금 이러고 있지 않을 것 같아서 그래
I mean, if the world
were gonna end today,
내 말은 오늘 당장
지구가 멸망한다면..
- why would you want to...?
- I- I hear you.
무슨 말인지 알아
I really do.
정말이야
But all those goals
I used to have-
하지만 내가 가졌던 목표들..
I still have 'em.
여전히 가지고 있어
Okay.
알겠어
Hey, sis?
저기 누나
The world's not gonna end today.
지구가 오늘
멸망하는 일 없을거야
I have very reliable sources.
아주 믿을만한 소식통이 있어
Wild night,
huh, buddy?
열광적인 밤이었지?
Nah. Pretty
standard Tuesday.
아니
평소랑 다를 것 없는 화요일이었지
This is bad.
This is very bad.
좋지 않아
정말 좋지 않아
Can't you see
that we're losing them, man?
쟤들을 잃고 있는거 보여?
I'm your best friend, Jeff.
내가 네 제일 친한 친구야 제프
No, I'm your best
friend, Chuck!
아니. 내가 네 제일 친한 친구야 척
Oh, isn't life grand!
인생 멋있지 않니!
Maybe we should form
an alliance.
우리 둘이서 동맹을 만들어야해
You and me could be
best friends?
우리끼리 친한 친구할까?
Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, dude.
진정해 친구
Let's not, uh...
제발..
Let's not panic
here, okay?
당황하지 말자고
Thanks, man.
고마워 척
Well, you know...
고맙긴 뭘
It was very
comfortable.
편하게 잘 잤어
Sure.
천만에
Excuse me.
실례할게요
We need to talk.
우리 얘기 좀 해요
My sister thinks
I'm an idiot, I know.
우리 누나가 날 멍청이로
생각한다고요? 나도 알아요
Actually, we just got
some fresh intel
방금 당신이 제일 좋아하는
on your favorite
video game designer.
게임 디자이너에 대한
새로운 정보를 입수했어요
There were a few things
Morimoto left out of his bio.
이력에서 몇 가지 찾아냈어요
Yeah. Guy secretly worked
for Japanese military.
응. 비밀리에 일본
군대에서 일한적이 있는데
In 1980, they
launched Morimoto's
1980년에 일본에서 모리모토의
첫 위성 무기를 발사했어
first-generation
weapons satellite.
The guy who created
Missile Command
미사일 커맨드를 만든 사람이
commands
actual missiles?
실제로 미사일을 지휘한다고요?
(Command 지휘하다)
Via satellite.
위성을 통해서
It's still up there-
위성이 아직도 거기 있어요
dormant,
but presumed operational.
작동이 중단되긴 했지만
사용은 가능하다고 해요
Anyone knows how
어떻게 해야 그게 작동할지 알겠지
모리모토야
to fire that puppy up,
it's Morimoto.
And you think he's working
with Farrokh and the terrorists?
그래서 테러리스트들과
일한다고 생각하는거예요?
Well, he hasn't been seen
in years.
몇 년째 종적이 묘연해
We captured this image
outside Morimoto's office
1시간 전쯤에 모리모토
사무실 밖에서 찍은 사진이야
about an hour ago.
What about Jeff?
제프는 어떻게 된거예요?
How is he supposed
to be involved in all this?
걔가 이 일에 어떻게 관련된거죠?
The only way
to find out is
그걸 알아내려면
아타리 본사로 들어가야해요
to get into
Atari headquarters.
Security's going to be tight.
경비가 삼엄할거야
But if we don't
secure the satellite,
하지만 위성을 지켜내지 못하면
then Jeff's safety is gonna be
the least of our concerns.
제프의 안전에는 신경 쓸
겨를이 없을거에요
So how do you want to do this?
어떻게 할거야?
Guys...
저기요
I have an idea.
저한테 좋은 생각이 있어요
All right, be
cool, Casey.
자 침착해요 케이시
Have you seen
what I'm wearing?
내가 입고 있는 옷 보여?
Just let me do
the talking, okay?
말은 내가 할게요
These are my people-
programmers, nerds.
나 같은 사람들이예요
프로그래머잖아요
And right now, their
network is being attacked
지금 회사 네트워크가
바이러스에 공격 받고 있어요
by a particularly
nasty virus.
Back at Stanford, we called
it the Bartowski special.
스탠포드 다닐 땐 그걸
바토스키 스페셜이라고 하곤 했어요
Yeah, real cool
there, Chuck.
그래 너나 진정해
Damn computers are out
all over the building.
망할 컴퓨터가 다 고장났어
Gentlemen,
excuse me.
저기요 실례합니다
What do you want?
뭐 때문에 오셨어요?
We heard you're having
a computer problem.
컴퓨터에 이상이
생겼다고 해서 왔는데요
Someone
called. Bill?
누가 전화를 주셔서요
빌이였나?
Bob... I can't
remember,
밥? 정확히는 기억이 안 나네요
exactly; it was a
very common name.
너무 흔한 이름이라서요
- Yeah, we got it covered.
- Mind if I take a peek?
- 우리가 알아서 할게요
- 제가 좀 봐도 될까요?
Look, nerd,
이봐요
Atari has
more Ph. D.s
아타리 사(社)엔 사기나 치는
than friggin'
Microsoft.
마이크로 소프트사(社)보다
박사가 더 많아요
Yeah. Why don't you help
가서 할머니 AOL 로그온하는거나
some old lady log onto AOL?
도와주지 그래요?
(AOL: 미국 메신저 이름)
Nice one. Ooh!
잘했어!
Plan B.
다음 계획
Hi.
안녕하세요
I hear you're having
a computer problem.
컴퓨터에 이상이
있다고 해서 왔는데요
See, if I could just get
onto that terminal, I could
제가 컴퓨터로 화재 경보기
울리고 전기를 끊어버리면
set off the fire alarm,
I couldcrash the power,
create a diversion.
시선을 돌릴 수 있을거예요
Or we could just
아님 그냥 계단으로 올라갈 수도 있지
take the stairs.
Looks like
Agent Walker's
워커가 알아서 시선을
잘 돌리고 있는것 같으니까
got the diversion
pretty well covered.
Sarah doesn't even know
how to fix a computer.
새라는 컴퓨터 고칠 줄 몰라요
The second she touches
that machine, our cover's blown.
컴퓨터를 만지기만해도
우리 정체가 들통날거에요
The CPUs have been
massively overvolted,
CPU가 타 버리긴 했지만
but we may be able to ghost
the drive on another system.
드라이브를 다른 시스템으로
옮길 수 있을 것 같아요
The more elegant solution
would be to flash the BIOS
그것 보단
BIOS를 재 기록하고
and swap out
the cooked CPU.
타 버린 CPU를 바꾸는게
더 낫겠죠
What are you guys waiting for?
안 가고 거기 서서 뭐해요?
Okay. I'm gonna
see if I can find
좋아. 난 가서 펜트하우스로
another way into
the penthouse.
갈 수 있는 다른 길이
있나 보고 올테니까
You wait here
where it's safe.
넌 안전하게 여기에 있어
This place is creepy.
여기 소름끼친다
So creepy.
정말 소름끼쳐
Well, if it isn't my friend
from the Buy More.
바이모어에서 만난 분이 아니신가요
What a funny coincidence
여기서 이렇게 만나다니
이런 재밌는 우연이 다 있네요
finding you here.
Yeah, it's
freakin' hilarious.
네 정말 재밌네요
What a small world, right?
세상 참 좁죠?
I got a... I got a
call about a computer
컴퓨터에 문제가 있다고
여, 연락을 받아서요
that was acting
up here, and so...
In fact, is this
the right floor?
이 층이 맞나요?
I don't even
know if it's...
여기가 맞는지 잘 모르..
You have the correct floor.
제대로 오셨어요
- This way. Please.
- You know if you're busy,
- 이 쪽으로 오시죠
- 혹시 바쁘시다면
I can come back
another time.
나중에 다시 올 수도 있는데요
Uh-uh. You're timing
was perfect.
아니요
아주 좋은 시간에 오셨어요
I hope
컴퓨터 때문에
크게 고생 안 하셨으면 좋겠군요
the machine doesn't give you
too much trouble.
* What you say
about his company *
* Is what you say
about society *
* Catch the mist,
catch the myth *
* Catch the mystery,
catch the drift *
You should not be here.
여기 계시면 안 돼요
Um, uh...
* The world is,
the world is... *
♪ The world is, the world is.. ♪
(Rush - Tom sawyer)
Mr. Morimoto?
모리모토 씨?
You listening
to Rush?
러쉬 노래 들으세요?
You are too late.
늦으셨네요
벌써 코드를 암호를 가져갔어요
He took the code.
Who are they, terrorists?
대체 그 사람들 누굽니까?
테러리스트예요?
I knew I should've
never hidden
이 기계 안에
암호를 숨기는게 아니였는데
the numbers inside
the machine.
You hid the satellite code
미사일 커맨드 게임 안에
위성 암호를 숨기셨어요?
inside a game of
Missile Command?
Every game, hidden
in the final board.
모든 게임에 숨겼는데
마지막판을 깨면 나타나요
The kill screen.
A secret level
only I could achieve.
저만 알고
저만 깰 수 있는 단계에요
The mathematics underlying
the final board
마지막판을 이루는 수학이
많이 진보했어요
are too advanced.
It's like the music
of the universe.
정말 세계적인 노래죠
Hands up.
손 들어
I am sorry, I
cannot do that.
미안하지만 그럴 수 없어요
- What's going on here, Chuck?
- Wait.
- 척 무슨 일이야?
- 잠시만요
Wait, if the bad guys
have the code,
잠시만요. 나쁜 놈들이
암호를 가져갔다면
why are you still
playing the game?
왜 아직도 게임을 하고 계세요?
Uh-oh.
이런
We're running out of time!
시간이 없어요!
SAVE YOURSELVES!
나가세요!
- Let's get out of here, Chuck.
- No, we can't just leave him here.
- 빨리 나가자 척
- 안 돼요. 어떻게 두고 가요
- Not this time.
- No, no, no, wait!
- 이번엔 내 말들어!
- 안 돼요 잠시만요!
Go, go, go!
It's a... wait, wait!
가세요! 빨리요!
THE END
General, we're
sorry to report
장군님. 파로크 일당이
암호를 가져갔습니다
that Farrokh and his
team have the code.
That, and they murdered
Morimoto.
그리고 모리모토 씨도 죽였고요
That means that your duties
are no longer required
즉 이번 작전에서 자네들이
더 이상 해줄 일은 없네
on this operation.
Casey,
케이시
이젠 밴더버그에 있는
we're turning this matter
over to the 30th Space Wing
30th Space Wing에서 해결할걸세
(미사일 발사 등으로 미국을 방어함)
at Vandenberg.
Wait, you're launching an ICBM?
대륙간 탄도 미사일을
발사 하시는거예요?
You think you can shoot
down that satellite
위성이 우릴 공격하기 전에
먼저 공격할 수 있다고 보세요?
before it
shoots us?
Morimoto's satellite
will be passing
모리모토의 위성이 4시간 후면
캘리포니아 위를 지나가
over California in four hours.
Best case,
we shoot it down
계획대로 된다면
그 쪽 위성 미사일이 장착되기전에
off the coast before its own
missiles are armed.
해안 쪽으로 떨어뜨릴 수 있을거야
The satellite
falls to Earth
무난한 정도 수의
사상자가 나오겠지
with acceptable
civilian casualties.
Wait a second, acceptable what?
잠시만요. 뭐가 무난하다고요?
잘 안 되면 어떻게 되는거죠?
I'd like to hear
the bad version.
We miss.
빗맞히는거지
What happens then?
그 다음엔 어떻게 되는데요?
Farrokh uses
Morimoto's satellite
파로크가 모리모토의 위성으로
세계 3차대전을 벌이겠죠
to start World War III.
Hey, what about the...
what about the kill screen?
그럼 그, 그 마지막 판은요?
- Excuse me? - Missile Command - Morimoto said
뭐라고? / 미사일 커맨드요
모리모토 씨가 모든 게임 안에
that the code is hidden
in every arcade game.
암호를 숨겨 뒀다고 했어요
If we can get to the kill
screen, we can get the code,
마지막 판까지 깬다면
암호를 얻을 수 있을거고
and then we can take control
of the satellite.
그럼 우리가 위성을
통제할 수 있을거예요
We'll have our engineers
take a...
우리 기관 엔지니어에게..
No, look, the only way to get
the code is by beating the game,
아니요. 암호를 얻을 유일한
방법은 게임을 깨는 거예요
and the only person
who can beat the game...
그걸 할 수 있는
유일한 사람은..
- Is
- burned to a crisp.
바싹 구워졌지
- I was talking about Jeff.
- So was I.
- 전 제프 얘길 하는거예요
- 나도야
Casey, you coordinate
with the Air Force
케이시. 척이
긴급 대책을 처리하는 동안
while Mr. Bartowski
자넨 공군 쪽과 협력하게
pursues his...
contingency plan.
But I promise you,
one way or another,
하지만 어찌됐든간에
난 반드시 위성을 쏠 거네
I am bringing
that satellite down.
You want me
to come out
게임에서 은퇴한 걸
접으란 소리야?
of Missile Command
retirement?
You're serious?
진심이야?
Deadly.
응 진심이야
I don't know, man.
글쎄
Come on, what's
the problem?
왜 그래
뭐가 문제야?
I guess I'm just cool
with resting on my laurels
난 지금처럼 예전의 영광을
누리면서 사는 것도 괜찮아
- and whatnot.
- But Jeff...
하지만 제프
you could be
the first guy
네가 마지막판을 깨는
첫 번째 사람이 될 수 있는 기회야
to ever get to
the kill screen.
Listen, it doesn't exist.
그런 건 없어
The kill screen's just a myth.
이 게임에 마지막판은 없어
I promise you, it's real,
and you're the only one
장담하는데 있어
그걸 깰 수 있는
who can do it.
사람은 너 밖에 없고
I'm a little out
of shape, mentally.
나 지금 꼴이 엉망이야
정신적으로
Jeff, it's just a
stupid video game!
제프
그냥 비디오 게임일 뿐이잖아!
That's where
you're wrong, Chuck.
그게 아니야 척
It's more
than a game.
단순히 그냥 게임이 아니야
Besides, what do you care
whether I play or not?
게다가 내가 게임을 하던 말던
네가 무슨 상관이야?
I guess I was just really moved
by what you said last night.
아마 어제 네가 했던
말 때문인가봐
- Huh?
- Oh, you remember.
무슨 말? / 기억 안 나?
Come on.
왜 이래
How you were
sick and tired
네가 이렇게 시시한 곳에서
일하는 걸 얼마나 지겨워했는지
of busting your ass
at this stupid store.
How you had this
incredible gift
네가 가진 소중한 재능을
that you couldn't wait
for the world to see.
얼마나 세상에 보이고 싶은지 말이야
Really? I said that?
내가? 그렇게 말했어?
Sure you did, Jeff.
응 그랬지 제프
About Missile Command?
- 미사일 커맨드를 그렇게까지?
- 너 정말 대단하더라
You were very compelling.
Okay, I'll do it.
좋아 할게
- I'll play.
- Buddy...
게임 할 게 / 제프
But first,
I'm gonna need provisions.
하지만 먼저
식량이 필요해
I need two bottles
grape cough syrup,
포도맛 감기약 2병하고
one pound M&Ms, no brown,
갈색은 뺀 엠엔엠 1파운드 준비해줘
and my lucky arcade game from
the Gas 'N Sip in Tarzana.
또 타자나, 가스 앤 십에 있는
내 행운의 게임기도
Done.
알았어
Really?
정말?
I want Anna
wearing a hula skirt
애나가 훌라댄스 치마 입고
fanning me with a palm frond.
야자나무 잎으로 부채칠 해줬으면 좋겠어
- HUH?
- I sweat profusely when I play.
뭐? / 게임할 때
땀이 줄줄 나거든요
And finally,
그리고 마지막으로
I need a crowd.
관중들이 필요해요
- I want you to get some of my old fans back.
- Come on.
- 예전 내 팬 몇 분을 불러주세요
- 이봐
The people that were into that
game are in their 40s now.
그 사람들은 지금쯤 40대일거라고
They have jobs, and wives,
직장도 있고 아내도 있고
아이들도 있고 또..
and kids and...
Hey, hey, hey-
Morgan, buddy.
저기 모건, 친구
Can you give me
a hand with this?
이거 옮기는 것 좀 도와줄래?
Why don't you just
go ask your buddy, Jeff?
네 친구 제프한테 부탁하지 그래?
He's in the break room.
걘 휴게실에 있어
We're putting together
this like video game
오늘 오후에 모여서
공개 비디오 게임하기로 했거든
exhibition-thingy
this afternoon.
Jeff's gonna make a run
제프가 미사일 커맨드
최고점을 깰 거야
at the all-time
Missile Command high score.
- Whoa.
- Hey, where are you going?
- 우와
- 모건 어디가?
Sounds like you two guys
got it all worked out.
너네 둘이서도 잘 하는 것 같길래
Morgan, I desperately
need your help, okay?
모건 제발 나 좀 도와줘
If Jeff doesn't break
the Missile Command record...
제프가 그 게임 기록을 못 깨면..
What, Chuck?
The world's gonna end?
뭔데?
지구가 멸망이라도 한대?
Look, all I know
is that I need your help.
모건. 정말 네 도움이 필요해
Okay, I can't do this
without you, buddy.
너 없인 못 해낼거야
못 한다구
I can't.
Hey, hey, was Jeff...
모건 모건. 제프가..
was Jeff the president
of his high school
제프가 고등학교 때
오디오 비디오 클럽 회장이었을까?
audio/video club?
Doubt it.
설마 / 4년 연속 맘마미아
공연 매니저였을까?
Was Jeff a roadie
for Mamma Mia
for four
straight summers?
Does Jeff own
his own smoke machine?
제프한테 스모크 머신은 있을까?
- No, but I do. Okay.
- Huh?
아니. 하지만 난 있지
해 줄게
Jeff is a loser, dude.
제프 그 불쌍한 놈
I'll see what I can do.
내가 할 수 있는건
다 해 줄게
You're the best, buddy.
네가 최고다 친구
Oh, and I'm gonna need
to borrow your girlfriend.
아 맞다
네 여자친구도 좀 빌릴게
- Oh, dude, she's all yours.
- Great.
- 그래. 마음대로 해
- 좋았어
JEFF BARNES TO PLAY EXHIBITION!
제프 반즈의 공개 게임
MISSILE COMMAND
미사일 커맨드
JEFF BARNES TO PLAY EXHIBITION!
MISSILE COMMAND
제프 반즈의 공개 게임
미사일 커맨드
THE GREAT ONE RETURNS
JEFF BARNES AT BUY MORE ASAP!
다시 돌아왔습니다
제프를 보러 바이모어로 오세요
Jeff! Jeff! Jeff! Jeff!
제프!
Jeff! Jeff!
I'm here at a Burbank
electronics store
전 지금 버뱅크에 있는
전자 상가에 나와있습니다
where a local man
prepares to break
지금 이 곳에서 한 시민이
the Missile Command record.
BLAST FROM THE PAST
A FADING STAR SEEKS NEW GLORY
미사일 커맨드의 기록을
깰 준비를 하고 있는데요
Now for those of you
25년 전에 태어나지
않으신 분들은 모르시겠지만
who weren't around
a quarter century ago,
Jeffrey Barnes
first made his mark on...
제프리 반즈 씨는 1983년..
...way back in 1983.
이름을 떨쳤습니다
Sarah, Sarah-
I know where Farrokh is.
새라 새라
파로크가 어딨는지 알아냈어요
The terrorists are using
a television station
그 사람들,
텔레비전 방송국을 이용해서
to control the satellite;
they're here in L.A.
위성을 통제하고 있어요
지금 LA에 있어요
Chuck flashed.
척이 떠올랐는데
He knows where they're
controlling the satellite.
테러리스트들이 어디서
위성을 통제하는지 알고 있대
There is still time
위성을 조준하기 전까지
아직 시간 남았어
before the satellite
is in range.
Maybe Chuck's right,
but there's nothing you can do
척 말이 맞다고 해도
암호가 없는 한
to stop it without the code.
우리가 할 수 있는 건 없어
Well, I'm going to go
to the news station.
어쨌든 난 방송국으로 갈게
Knock yourself out.
I have my orders.
마음대로 해
난 명령 받은 게 있어
33 minutes and five
seconds, this finger
33분 5초 후면
이 손가락이 저 버튼을 누를거야
gonna push
that button.
Hmm. I'll call you
from the road.
나중에 전화할게
- Agent Walker.
- Yes.
워커 요원 / 응
Who do you trust to bring down
a rogue satellite more:
이 작전에서 누굴 더 믿어?
some burnout loser
playing a video game
비디오 게임이나 하는
힘 없는 놈이야
or an Air Force ICBM?
아님 미사일 쏘는 공군이야?
I trust Chuck.
난 척을 믿어
Jeff! Jeff! Jeff! Jeff! Jeff!
제프!
I'd like you all to meet
제프리 반즈씨가 나와계십니다
Jeffrey Barnes.
제프리 반즈
Uh...
Missile Command
미사일 커맨드의
world champ.
세계 챔피언이십니다
I don't feel so hot.
나 못 하겠어
What? No, no, no.
뭐? 아니 아니야
You're gonna be great.
You look great.
잘 해낼거야
잘 할 수 있어
You're gonna
kill it, buddy.
가서 깨버려
What was I thinking, man?
내가 무슨 생각을 했던거지?
No one can get
the kill screen.
마지막판 같은건 있지도 않은데
I can't handle the math.
수학 같은건 몰라
You've dedicated three years
지난 3년 내내
미사일 커맨드를 하시면서..
of your life to playing
Missile Command.
It's too heavy.
너무 힘들다고
It feels like my brain
is about to...
나 지금 뇌가..
What's next for Jeff Barnes,
다음 목표가 뭐죠?
Missile Command world champ?
미사일 커맨드의 세계 챔피언
Get up for
a second.
일어나봐
Hey.
제프
I'll get some water.
내가 물 가져올게
Hey, we-we-we need
to take care of this.
우린 가서
상황 정리하고 오자
Yeah.
Here I come.
Hey, hey.
제프
Come on, buddy,
come on!
제발 제프. 제발!
Wake up, buddy!
You got to play!
일어나 제프!
게임 해야지!
You got to get the kill screen,
you got to get the code.
마지막판을 깨야 암호를 알아낼 수 있단 말이야
If we don't stop that
satellite, they're gonna launch
그 위성을 막지 못하면
곧 그 사람들이 미사일을
some crazy missile into
space and then-then...
미친듯이 쏴댈꺼고
그럼..
then it's World War III.
세계 3차 대전이 일어날거야
Acceptable civilian casualties.
사상자들이 생긴댔어..
Oh, my God.
세상에
Hey, Chuck, what's up?
응 척. 무슨 일이야?
Hey, I was thinking,
응. 내가 생각해 봤는데
why don't you guys
get out of town, maybe
누나랑 캡틴이랑 둘이서 잠시
Palm Springs, you and Awesome
just get out of town.
팜 스프링스 같은 데로
놀러 갔다 오는게 어때?
Now, actually,
would be a great time.
지금 가면 딱 좋을 것 같아
Trip's on me, you know.
경비는 다 내가 댈게
- Early wedding present.
- Wait a minute.
- 이른 결혼 선물이라 생각해
- 잠시만
Are you trying to get rid of me?
지금 나 쫓아내려는거니?
No, no, I just
thought it'd be nice.
아니 아니
그냥 여행가면 좋을 것 같아서
What's gotten into you?
너 갑자기 왜 그래?
I don't know.
나도 몰라
Look, I'm sorry, okay?
누나 미안해
I- I know I've been a bit
of a disappointment lately.
내가 요즘 실망만 줬다는거 알아
I- I-I want you
to be proud of me.
누나가 날 자랑스럽게 여겼으면 좋겠어
I just... I ran out of time,
that's all.
시간이 모자라
그래서 그래
Why don't we talk about this
when you get home?
집에 와서 얘기 하는게 어때?
I got to run.
가봐야겠어
I love you, Ellie.
사랑해 누나
Honey,
자기
do you think my brother's
on drugs?
내 동생이 마약하는걸까?
That'd explain a lot.
그렇다면 많은 게 설명되지
They're going nuts
out there, okay?
사람들이 화내기 시작했어
These nerds are gonna
tear this joint apart.
저 사람들이 매장을 뒤집어 놓을거야
You got to do
something.
어떻게 좀 해봐
What am I supposed to do?
어떻게 하지?
Well, they came to see
video game greatness.
비디오 게임을
보러 온 사람들이니까
Someone better deliver.
다른 사람이라도 해야겠지
Ladies and gentlemen...
신사 숙녀 여러분
or Gentlemen,
아니 신사분들
let me introduce you
to the challenger.
오늘의 도전자입니다!
Hailing from the City of Angels,
the Master of Disaster...
LA 출신으로
재앙의 지배자
What's going on?
...the King of Sting,
고통의 왕
(영화 록키에 나오는 헤비급 세계 챔피언)
the Dancing Destroyer,
춤추는 파괴자라는 별명을 가진
(아폴로 크리드의 별명들)
Charles Irving
찰스 어빙 바토스키를 소개합니다!
Bartowski!
Who is this guy?
Where's
Jeff Barnes?
Who authorized this?
이거 누가 허가한거야?
This is an abomination.
정말 말도 안 되는군
THE END
You suck, Bartowski.
바토스키 진짜 못 한다
Are you listening to Rush?
러쉬 음악 들으세요?
Music of the universe.
정말 세계적인 노래죠
Missile Command.
미사일 커맨드
The mathematical pattern
underlying the game
게임을 이루는 수학적 패턴이
정확하게 똑같..
is exactly the same as-
Morgan.
모건
Hey, uh, buddy,
모건. 우리 매장에 러쉬 CD 있어?
do, do we carry any Rush CDs
in the store?
No need, I got 'em
all on my Zune.
CD 없어도 돼
내 준에 다운 받아놨어
You have a Zune?
너 준도 있어?
(마이크로 소프트에서 만든 MP3)
Are you kidding me? No.
No, I'll grab my iPod.
장난해? 없지
가서 아이팟 가져올게
Good, good, good,
I have, I have
좋아 잘 됐어
나 신청곡이 있어
a very,
very special request.
On my mark.
내가 셀게
Three, two, one.
3, 2, 1
Mark!
시작!
♪ Rush - Tom sawyer ♪
* A modern-day warrior-
mean, mean stride *
♪ A modern day warrior
mean, mean stride ♪
* Today's Tom Sawyer-
mean, mean pride... *
♪ Today's Tom Sawyer
mean, mean pride... ♪
* Though his mind is not
for rent *
♪ Though his mind is not for rent ♪
* Don't put him down
as arrogant *
♪ Don't put him down as arrogant ♪
* His reserve, a quiet defense *
♪ His reserve, a quiet defense ♪
* Riding out the day's events *
♪ Riding out the day's events ♪
* The river... *
♪ The river... ♪
WEAPONS SEQUENCE INITIATED
Welcome to Strategic Air
Command, Major Casey.
케이시 소령님
미 전략 공군입니다
* What you say
about his company *
♪ What you say about his company ♪
* Is what you say
about society *
♪ Is what you say about society ♪
* Catch the mist,
catch the myth *
♪ Catch the mist catch the myth ♪
* Catch the mystery,
catch the drift... *
♪ Catch the mystery
catch the drift... ♪
Engaging telemetry.
원격 측정을 시작하겠습니다
Arming warhead.
탄두를 장착합니다
And opening silo door.
격납고 문을 열겠습니다
* No, his mind is not for rent *
♪ No, his mind is not for rent ♪
* To any God or government *
♪ To any God or government ♪
* Always hopeful,
yet discontent *
♪ Always hopeful, yet discontent ♪
* He knows changes
aren't permanent... *
♪ He knows changes aren't permanent.. ♪
Give me the code.
암호가 뭐야
It was destroyed.
다 파기됐어
I'm gonna do this.
내가 해낼거야
No one can stop
the satellite now!
그 누구도 위성을 막을 수 없어!
Tell me what
the target is.
타겟이 뭐야
- What's the satellite aimed at?
- Why?
- 위성이 어딜 겨누고 있는거야?
- 왜? 상관 없잖아
It doesn't matter.
No one will remember
who threw the first stone.
누가 시작했는지는
아무도 기억 못 할텐데
- Oh, my God.
- Gentlemen,
세상에 / 여러분
we have a kill screen.
완결판이예요
I got this.
내가 해낼거야
Target's to range.
타겟을 겨냥합니다
Releasing synchronized safeties.
동시 안전 장치를 해제하겠습니다
On my mark.
제가 세겠습니다
Three,
two, one, mark.
2, 1. 시작
CONGRATULATIONS, MR. MORIMOTO.
WOULD YOU LIKE TO PLAY AGAIN?
YES NO
축하합니다 모리모토씨
계속 게임 하시겠습니까?
NO
OZPGSB
Fire when ready, sir.
준비 되시면 발사하십시오 소령님
Chuck, what's happening?
척 어떻게 됐어요?
Sarah, I did it!
새라 내가 해냈어요!
I did it, I beat the game.
해냈어요 깼어요!
I got to the kill screen.
마지막판까지 가서 암호를 알아냈어요!
I got the code!
The game- it follows a pattern.
게임이 패턴을 따르더라고요
It's just like
Mr. Morimoto said-
모리모토 씨가 말씀하신 것 처럼..
the music of the universe.
세계적인 음악이였어요
Chuck, just give me the code.
척. 암호 알려줘요
Oscar...
O
Zelda...
Z
Penguin...
P
Gamma...
G
Sector...
S
Bob...
B
WEAPONS SEQUENCE TERMINATED
Oh, my God.
세상에
Satellite's powering down.
위성 활동이 중단됐다
Terminate launch sequence.
발사를 취소한다
This bogey's
bugging out
놈들이 내빼고 집으로 가버렸군
and going home.
Damn.
젠장
You did it, Chuck.
해냈네요 척
It worked!
당신이 해냈어요
How does it feel to be a hero,
영웅이 된 기분이 어떠세요
바토스키 씨?
Mr. Bartowski?
Oh. Oh.
Looks like you fools had
one hell of a party.
자네 멍청이들끼리 굉장한 파티를 벌였더군
Congratulations,
Bartowski.
축하하네 바토스키
That's quite
an achievement.
큰 업적을 세웠더군
And in light
of today's events,
오늘의 사건들을 고려해서
I'd like to announce
누가 새 부매니저가
될지 발표하겠다
there's a new assistant
manager amongst us.
What'd I tell you, man?
내가 뭐랬어?
이제 곧 '바토스키'라고 할거야
It's all coming up
Bartowski.
You all remember
Mr. Emmett Milbarge.
다들 에밋 밀바지 씨 기억하지?
Mr. Milbarge has
volunteered to stay on
에밋 씨께서 여기 계시겠다고
자원하셨다
for...
well, as long as it takes.
일이 해결될 때까지 쭉
That's right, Michael.
맞습니다 마이클
I'm afraid this
branch is sick.
이 곳에 큰 문제가 있어
걱정이 됩니다
And not the kind of sick that
can be fixed with a Band-Aid.
게다가 밴드를 붙인다고
금방 고쳐질 문제도 아니죠
What this Buy More needs
requires a surgeon.
이 곳에 필요한 것은
바로 외과의사입니다
Someone who doesn't mind
끈기 있게 일을 해낼 수 있는
외과 의사 말이죠
getting up to their
elbows in guts.
Mmm.
And that's exactly
what I'm gonna do.
앞으로 제가 할 일은 이겁니다
I'm gonna reach in,
손을 뻗어서
wrap my fingers
around the disease,
제 손가락으로 그 병폐를 감싸고
and rip... it... out.
확.. 뜯어버리겠어요
How you feeling, buddy?
제프 좀 어때?
- Better.
- Good.
나아졌어 / 잘 됐네
Thanks.
고마워
So...
그래..
Missile Command champion.
미사일 커맨드 챔피언이 됐네
I got lucky.
운이 좋았던거야
You know.
Congrats.
축하해
I'm glad it was you.
그게 너여서 다행이야
I mean, you're sure
you're not...
내 말은 너 정말..
Me? Uh-uh.
나? 아냐
괜찮아
I'm cool.
Being number one
is a real bitch.
일인자가 되는거
정말 못할 짓이야
Feels like the whole world is
gunning for you, sometimes.
가끔은 전 세계가 날 노리고
있는 것만 같은 기분이거든
I can imagine.
알 것 같다
So, what was it like?
그건 어땠어?
The kill screen?
마지막판 깬거 말이야
Forget it.
못 들은걸로 해
I'll see you tomorrow.
내일 보자
Oh,
I am so proud of you!
척 정말 대견하다!
Hey, relax.
누나 진정해
It's just a video game.
겨우 비디오 게임인데 뭘
Granted, I am the best Missile
Commander in the world.
맞아. 내가 미사일 커맨드
세계 챔피언이야
I'm not talking
about a stupid video game.
시시한 게임 같은 걸
얘기 하는게 아니야
I'm talking about this.
이거 얘기 하는거야
Sarah told us
what's inside.
새라가 이 안에 뭐가
들었는지 다 알려줬어
My diploma?
내 졸업장?
Well, don't act
so surprised.
놀란 척 하지마
You sly dog.
이 능글맞은 놈
Sarah also told us about
우리 몰래 뭘 하고 있었는지도
what you've been doing
behind our backs.
새라가 다 얘기해줬어
She did?
새라가?
Really?
정말?
Yeah. No wonder you've
been such a mess
응. 그래서 작년에
그렇게 엉망이었구나
- this past year.
- Why didn't you
왜 온라인으로 강의 듣는다고
얘기 안했니?
tell us that you were
taking online courses?
Oh!
아!
Oh, right... that.
그래.. 그거 말하는거구나
You two kids have some
celebrating to do.
둘이서 축하하고 와
She's waiting
out back.
저 쪽에서 기다리고 있어
You'll thank me for that ginseng
shake in the morning.
내가 아침에 준
쉐이크가 도움이 될거야
You really surprised me,
Charles.
찰스, 너 때문에 정말 놀랐어
Well, thanks for
my fake diploma.
가짜 졸업장 고마워요
- What do you mean?
- I get it.
- 무슨 소리예요?
- 다 알아요
You know, you had one
of your CIA pal's
누나가 나한테 잔소리 그만하게 하려고
doctor it up to get
Ellie off my back.
새라 동료가 만들어 준거 아니예요
It's real, Chuck.
척 그거 진짜예요
Come on.
말도 안돼요
I'm serious.
You graduated.
진짜에요. 졸업한거예요
What about my last
12 credits?
12학점이 모자른데요?
Well, Casey and I decided
케이시랑 내가
척이 해준 뛰어난
that your exceptional
field service
현장 근무를 가치있다고 여겼고
ought to count
for something
and Stanford agreed.
스탠포드에서도 동의했어요
Huh.
And by exceptional,
you mean, like, uh,
뛰어난 현장 근무라면..
I don't know, decrypting
weapons-satellite codes?
위성 무기 암호를 해독한거요?
Electrical Engineering.
그건 전기 공학이죠
Or running away from
exploding games
미사일 커맨드 게임기가
폭파하는데 도망친거는요?
of Missile Command?
Physical Education.
그건 체육이고요
You earned it, Chuck.
척은 받을 자격 있어요
Thank you.
고마워요
You see that star out there
on the horizon?
저기 반짝거리는거 보여요?
That's the Air Force
지금 공군이 모리모토씨의
bouncing Morimoto's satellite
off the atmosphere
위성을 대기에서
튕겨내서 태우는거예요
and burning it up.
Make a wish.
소원 빌어요
It's yours.
당신 몫이예요
Hey, bud.
안녕 친구
Let's party.
파티를 시작해볼까
팎읔襟俚캥莉
-==http://www.ragbear.com==-
뻑短속흙
네이트 드라마 24 자유제작
(http://www.nate.com/24)